Work hard, you two!
We will.
Catarina, remember to mind
your manners at school.
Don't lift up your skirt,
eat food off of the floor,
or throw your toys, even accidentally.
And don't be noisy late at night—
I-I'll be fine, Mother.
We'll be going now!
Sister!
Goodbye, then.
Good luck.
The time has finally come.
Here at this magic academy
is where the game starts.
HameFura, I Reincarnated
into an
Otome Game
as a
Villainess
with only
destruction flags···
aimaina I my me datte guruguru mazetara
If you mix it round and round it becomes unclear
akogare no kyuu tenkai ni niau kamo ne
With an unexpected development, maybe it will look good
ren ai nara iza morase
If it's love, express it now
tobikiri no dessert
with wonderful desserts
amazuppai cho misu wa oyurushi asobase
An addictive sweet and sour mix, I'm sorry to have fun
mawaru uruwashiki koi moyou
Love is a spiral pattern that spins on and on
chotto souzou naname you he massugu susume
I need to stop and think before moving forward
otome no route wa hitotsu janai
A maiden's route is not just one!
hatto suru lucky na ima ni gokigen you
My heart feels surprisingly lucky now
itsudatte maemukina desu
And so I will remain optimistic
ai mo kawarazu ni touhonseisou kou kando wo agete
If you want to win the game of love, you have to risk it all
kiyoku tadashiku utsukushiku are to wa yoku itta monda na
It's a pure, intense and beautiful feeling, so fight for it
kitto warui happy na mirai ni gokigen you
I still don't know if my ending will be happy or not
itsu datte maemukina desu
But I will remain optimistic
Episode 4
I Enrolled in the Magic Academy...
Right this way, please.
It's beautiful.
I'll bring the rest of your things.
Okay, thank you.
This is where the otome game
Fortune Lover is set.
The game's heroine should be here, too.
Most people with magic have noble lineage,
but she's a commoner.
On top of that, she has
very rare light magic.
The extraordinary Maria.
Whether I meet my doom or not depends on
how romance develops between her
and the four conquerable characters.
So it has begun at last.
Yes, but many things in the past seven
years have differed from the game.
Let's review the information we have.
First is Geordo Stuart.
In the game, Geordo has no
interest in Catarina at all...
But now, he and Catarina get along great!
But I wonder why he still won't
break off the engagement...
My would has healed, so you don't
have to take responsibility anymore.
You can break off the engagement.
The wound hasn't healed.
I will never break off our engagement.
Catarina is nothing more to Geordo
than an excuse to turn down other women!
The way he grew into a beautiful,
dark-hearted prince is just like the game.
Second is our adopted brother, Keith.
As a result of our efforts,
he grew up to be not a frivolous
playboy, but a fine young man.
Though he's grown quite handsome lately,
so he's unconsciously turning
into a playboy anyway.
Third is Alan Stuart.
His inferiority complex toward his
twin brother Geordo was resolved,
and his musical talent has blossomed.
And unlike in the game, his fiancée,
Mary, isn't attracted to him.
Fourth is Nicol Ascart.
He remains silent and expressionless,
but his devilish allure
is even more powerful.
We even made friends
with his little sister, Sophia!
Just how will these changes
affect future events?
I don't know, but our only option
is to move forward!
Yeah!
This academy is the largest
in the Kingdom of Sorcier.
We have our own Department of Magic
for the research of magic,
and students who achieve superior marks
are permitted to join
the Department of Magic after graduation.
The game's heroine should be here, too.
You will spend the next
two years studying here
to better yourselves as well as this kingdom,
Is something wrong?
Oh, um, no...
and learning how to use magic properly.
Oh, that's right.
Why don't you come to my room after this?
I have some unusual sweets.
Okay.
Next, we will hear from
the student council president.
I'd like to congratulate you all
on your acceptance to this academy.
I'm the student council
president, Sirius Dieke.
I'm sure there will be things
that worry or confuse you at first,
but if you need anything,
the student council is here to support you.
Let's work together to make our
time here both fun and meaningful.
Welcome.
Thanks for having me.
And me!
Why did you come along with her, Keith?
I asked our servant to inform me immediately
if anything happened to my sister.
I wasn't expecting you
to make a move so soon.
Don't you think you're taking
your meddling a bit far?
Prince Geordo, can I really eat these?
Of course. I got them just for you.
I'll dig in, then!
Delicious!
By the way, I met a girl
here who has light magic.
Oh, yes, the girl all the students
have been talking about.
Yes. She seemed to be lost,
so I saw her to her dorm.
Th-That was the first meeting
between Geordo and the game's heroine!
Geordo
A
You're climbing a tree dressed like that?
You're climbing a tree dreessed like that?
You must be quite a tomboy.
Maria
A
I got lost, so I thought I'd try
to see where I was from up high.
I got lost.  I thought I'd try
Geordo
A
I see. You were lost.
In that case, I'll see you to your dorm.
This really is unfolding just like the game.
That encounter makes Geordo
take interest in the heroine,
Romance Flag
and pretty soon,
he'll fall in love with her!
So there are other girls besides
my sister who climb trees in skirts?
I'm used to seeing that by now,
so I wasn't too surprised,
but she seemed quite flustered.
I suppose anyone would be.
My sister, on the other hand...
Catarina is certainly an exception.
I find that part of her charming, though.
After Geordo falls for the heroine,
Catarina, who he only got engaged
to out of necessity, becomes a hindrance...
Are you listening, Catarina?
She's not listening at all.
I can't believe Geordo's on the verge
of being conquered right after enrolling here.
They say falling in love changes people,
so there's no telling what'll happen.
I can't let my guard down.
So today's the first day of classes.
Yes, so it is.
Oh, that's right.
I met the girl with light magic
that Prince Geordo mentioned.
Wh-Wh-Wha—
S-Sister? What's wrong?
In the game, Keith and the heroine
meet when he hits on her!
Did you hit on her?!
Wh-What? "Hit on" her?
Um...
It means to talk a girl into
doing immoral things, I guess...
I-Immoral things?!
You know I would never do that!
Then how did you meet her?
She dropped her handkerchief,
so I picked it up for her!
A handkerchief?
After failing to pick up the heroine,
Keith picks up her handkerchief
and goes after her again!
Keith
A
This is yours, right?
If you want it back, have some fun with me.
If you want it back,  have some fun with me.
What happened to the handkerchief?!
I just gave it back to her.
I see...
Tell me... What was she like?
What was...
She was just a nice girl.
She thanked me politely and everything.
Not that, Keith! That's not what I'm asking!
Huh?
Did you fall in love with her?!
Fall in l-l-l-l-love?!
Wh-Wh-What... d-do you...
That shocked reaction...
I hit the nail on the head.
So I was right.
You're already in love with her.
Sister... Seriously,
what are you talking about?
It's fine. You don't need to hide it.
There's just one thing I want to tell you...
That I have no intention of getting
between you and the girl you love!
I'll be cheering you on!
I won't get in the way!
Huh? Keith?
Lady Catarina, I think you've done enough.
Keith-sama clearly can't take any more.
First it was Geordo, and now it looks
like Keith's about to be conquered...
The game's heroine, Maria Campbell.
Magic is divided into five types:
water, fire, earth, wind, and light.
It is crucial to understand
your own magical attribute
and learn how to handle it effectively.
Now, open your textbooks.
Claes-san, please open your textbook.
Pay attention during class!
Y-Yes, sir!
Catarina-sama, is something wrong?
Huh?
If you feel unwell, just say so.
I'll look after you day and night.
Thanks... but I'm fine.
Sophia.
Brother!
How's school? Are you getting used to it?
Yes.
I'm in the same dorm and the same
classes as Catarina-sama and Mary-sama,
so I'm having a lot of fun!
I see.
We're only separated in our practical class.
I can't use anything but my Earth Bump,
even though Keith can make earth dolls
and even move them...
Don't worry. Everyone's magic is different.
I have wind magic, the same as my brother,
but I can't use it as skillfully as he can.
Really?
Mary, you have water magic,
just like Prince Alan, right?
Yes, but I've never seen
Prince Alan use magic.
I've never seen Prince
Geordo use magic, either.
I heard he has fire magic, but...
Royals don't use their magic carelessly.
He killed me with a sword in the game, too...
Wait! This is no time to be so carefree!
Maria is incredibly attractive.
It's only a matter of time
before Geordo falls for her!
We will now commence this
meeting to discuss our strategy
for avoiding the doom ending.
Maria-san is more charming than I imagined.
It's true that Maria is super attractive,
but it's not like Mary
and Sophia are any worse!
Sophia and Mary, two of the heroine's rivals,
are both smart and proficient in magic.
They're both gorgeous, too!
Maria can't beat them that easily!
If she could beat anyone, it's Catarina,
who's short on both brains and magic!
Yes, exactly!
What a relief...
That's not a relief at all!
If Catarina loses to her, it's all over!
We'll be on a one-way path to the doom ending!
Catarina loses to
the heroine
and Catarina is doomed
That's right! We don't want to lose!
What do we do?!
What do we do?! What do we do?!
Let's raise a farm.
A farm?
In case we end up being exiled,
we should gain experience in farming
in order to get by as a farmer.
Then we will focus on farming henceforth.
Are we in agreement?
No objections!
Lady Catarina...
This is the flower garden, is it not?
Yes, it is.
I got the school's permission.
But, Lady Catarina, those don't
look like flower seedlings.
What are you talking about, Anne?
These will grow cucumber flowers,
and these will grow eggplant flowers.
In other words, they're
vegetable seedlings...
Well, yes, they will
ultimately grow into vegetables,
but before that, they'll grow flowers!
Please take care not to let
the school find out this is a farm.
Catarina-sama!
We're going to have a tea party with—
S-Sister...
Catarina...
You're still messing
with that stuff, even here?
That look suits you.
Yes, it puts the mind at ease.
Really? Thanks!
It's a rule at this school that the students
who score high on tests
join the student council.
Just like in the game, as expected,
1st      Geordo Stuart
2nd      Maria Campbell
3rd      Alan Stuart
Geordo and his brother earned top scores.
Geordo placed highest in the school, huh?
And you came in third, Prince Alan.
You're both fantastic.
How'd you do?
I'm 80th. As average as they come!
Uh... I see.
And Maria Campbell is second...
In the game, Alan sees Maria
as a rival after she tops his score
and picks fights with her.
And once he falls in love with her...
Um, are you unhappy with your rank?
No. I don't really care
about winning or losing.
People have things they're good at
and things they're bad at,
so there's no point in worrying
about every little thing.
Anyway, one of the teachers suggested
I play a recital here at school.
What do you think?
That sounds great!
A lot of people look forward
to hearing you play.
Would you...
Do you want to hear it, too?
Huh? Yes, of course!
Okay.
Then, I'll put on a recital.
Student Council Office
My friends joining the student council
was just like in the game.
What was different about it
was that I started going to
the student council office a lot, too.
Thank you for the tea.
I'm not interrupting your work, am I?
No, not at all.
Since the first-years joined,
my work is much easier, anyway.
Speaking of, you and Nicol-sama
are the only second-years, right?
Yes. There were more of us before,
He's mine!
but they kept getting into fights over Nicol.
No, he's mine!
Like hell! He's mine!
Nicol's devilish charm
is in full swing here, too.
I'll be working over there.
Let me know if you need anything.
Okay, thank you.
Since the president welcomes me so warmly,
I've found myself spending
a lot more time here.
And, of course,
that leads to interactions
with the other council members...
Claes-sama...
Please help yourself to these, if you'd like.
Thank you, Campbell-san.
Maria-chan's such a nice, sweet girl!
I'll have some, then.
These are delicious!
They were a gift given
to the student council.
By the way, do you ever bring
any of the sweets you make?
Huh?
Wait, did I just...
Make some sweets for me!
...make that sound like a threat?!
U-Um, that is...
I don't mean to force you
into making them or anything...
Um... How did you know that I make sweets?
U-Uh...
I can't tell her I saw it in a game!
I think I heard it from one
of the cooks in the cafeteria...
Oh, so that's it.
I do borrow the school's kitchen
to make sweets sometimes.
But I don't make anything good
enough to serve the council...
I do like high-class sweets,
but I love homemade ones, too!
What? You do?
Yes!
The head maid at my mansion used to
make sweets for me all the time.
I've been missing the taste
of those sweets since I came here...
Oh, I see.
If you don't mind,
I'd be really happy
if you'd share a few with me...
Okay.
I don't know if you'll like them,
but I'll make some for you sometime.
Thanks!
I've waited so long to eat
Maria-chan's homemade sweets!
Hm? What's this?
Something smells delightfully
fragrant and delicious...
It's coming from over there!
Campbell-san!
Don't think you're special
because everyone fawns over you!
You were going to give the student
council cheap food made by a commoner?
These couldn't be more unfit for them!
Stop it!
C-Catarina Claes-sama?
What do all of you think you're doing?
What have they done
to Maria-chan's homemade sweets?
Such a crime... is unforgivable!
W-We're so sorry!
Having the face
of a villainess paid off bigtime.
But, gosh...
These smell so good!
Delicious!
It's gentle on the tongue
and has the perfect level of sweetness!
This would rank among
the best sweets in history!
I'm stuffed!
O-Oh, no!
I got carried away and ate them all!
I-I'm sorry!
No, I don't mind that...
It's just that those were on the ground...
They only fell onto the grass.
They were hardly dirty at all,
so there's no problem!
I-I see...
But really,
these are just as good
as anything a professional would make!
They were delicious!
Thank you.
Sh-She's so cute!
No wonder she's an otome game heroine!
This would make anyone's heart skip a beat!
So this is where you've been.
What are you doing?
Catarina?
U-Um...
Extra Strong Fertilizer
I had no idea Maria-chan
was being bullied like that.
Ugh! They're so mean!
They're just like Catarina in the game!
Wait...
Come to think of it, there was
a scene like that in the game...
Oh! She's remembered!
The one who bullied Maria
in the game was Catarina!
And the one who defended Maria was him.
Stop it!
These are truly delicious!
He's the best!
This was a major event in the advancement
of Geordo and Maria's romance in the game.
But the one who actually defended Maria
and ate the sweets was...
We took Geordo's event away from him!
Now their romance won't make any progress.
It's better if it doesn't!
If things work out between them,
Catarina is doomed!
Y-You're right...
How truly splendid that she broke her
doom flag without meaning to.
Well done! Way to go, Catarina!
Yeah!
All right!
I'll keep working my tail off!
kokoro ga tsukiru made moyase
My heart yearns for you so much
kantan ni clear dekiru
I thought it was easy to clear
koi wa game sou omotteta
To win at this love game
gururi madowasete hikiyosete
I'm spinning around and pulling you in
otosu shudai wo narabuke wo
Following along in my footsteps
naze kimi dakara igai
Why are you so captivating?
dono route erabeba saita nano ka
Which route will be the best choice?
kotae wa mienai
I can't find the answer
Bad End no unmei demo boku no mono ni nareba ii
Even if fate leads me to a "Bad End", it's fine
sou saa douse hametsu suru no nara kimi to
You're the one I want in my life
zettai ni zetsumei shinai aida to chikaukara
My love for you will never change
ubai saa nareru kakugo
Prepare to be conquered
mubou mi de muteki nayosashisa mudai makichirasu mae ni
You make me feel invincible, imprudent and happy at the same time
sono chisen wo hitorijime shitte miseru
I want to find out more about you
donna kodoku mo itami mo
No matter how much the pain is
kimi goto uketomeru
I will carry it for you
machi ukeru zetsubou mo nozomu tokoro
Even if despair awaits me, I'll take it on